funology.com 2018-11-13

# Privacy Policy: Funology

We want you to have a good time at Funology.com, learn things, and be safe. We respect our visitors’ privacy. This is why we promise:

  * We will never publish last names, addresses, phone numbers, or any other information that identifies you. If you send this information to Funology as part of a message, we will delete it before we post the message on the site.
  * If you prefer that your messages not be posted on the site or published in any print materials–and you tell us so–we will honor your request. We will even delete those messages from our files. (Contact us by e-mail should you ever want us to delete a message.)
  * Our Web server automatically collects your domain name and keeps track of the pages that you access or visit. But this information is never connected with your name.
  * If you submit ideas or content to us, you admit that you are the owner of that content and are granting us permission to reproduce it on our website.
  * We may conduct surveys from time to time. We will share the information with our partners and sponsors, but only in aggregate form (for example, the number of boys or girls of a certain age who visit the site) and we will not identify anyone by their full name.
  * We do not request any credit card or other financial information. While we screen our partners carefully, we are not responsible for the content or safety and privacy practices at any sites linked from our pages.

Typically, you may visit our website without informing us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Some sections of our site may ask for personal information such as name, address and telephone number or e-mail address, and if you decline to give it to us we may be unable to fulfill your request. We collect only the information we need to respond to you or to process your online transaction. We do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise share personal information collected on our website with third parties.

Our Web server automatically recognizes only your domain name but NOT your e-mail address. Aggregate information that we collect (e.g., total number of page views on a given day) is used for internal review of traffic patterns to our site. We collect your e-mail address if you communicate with us by e-mail or otherwise voluntarily provide your e-mail address to us, and we collect other information that you volunteer.

If you supply us with your e-mail address online, you may receive e-mail contact from us with information on updates to our website or about special programs or events in which you might be interested. If you prefer not to receive future emails, simply send an e-mail to inquiries (at) funology.com using “Please Remove this Email Address” as the subject heading.

We do not share personal information gathered via our website with other commercial entities. We may, however, share some aggregate information (number of “hits,” types of visitors, etc.) with our partner companies.

The website is intended for use by persons 18 years and older. This website does not knowingly collect any information about children under the age of thirteen.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**Embedded content from other websites**

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies used for tracking are anonymous. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies but you can control cookies through your browser preference settings.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

**Analytics cookies**

Analytics cookies collect information about the use of our website, and enable us to improve the way it works. For example, analytics cookies show us the most frequently visited pages, and analyzes site traffic. We use them to look at overall patterns of usage on the site, rather than the usage of any particular individual.

We may also use Google Analytics to collect information regarding visitor behavior and visitor demographics on some of our services, and to develop website content. This analytics data is not tied to any Personal Information. For more information about Google Analytics, please visit <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>. You can opt out of Google’s collection and Processing of data generated by your use of the Services by going to <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

**How do I manage cookies?**

You can disable cookies through the settings on your browser. You may wish to refer to <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/browsers/index.html>for information on commonly used browsers. You can follow the instructions on your browser’s help page or their website to remove the cookies set by our site and other sites. You can also choose to block our site and other sites from setting these cookies in the future.

To opt-out of analytics cookies by Google Analytics, please go to <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

**Advertising**

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. We use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and we disclaim all liability in connection therewith.

**Social media widgets**

Our site may include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, Facebook Share, Facebook Messenger, Google+, and other similar features or interactive mini-programs that run on our Site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the features to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a Third Party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.

**Comments**

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: <https://automattic.com/privacy/>. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

**How long we retain your data**

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

**What rights you have over your data**

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

**Where we send your data**

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**How to opt out of cookies and interest-based advertising.**

As noted above, you may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or remove them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences. Please note that cookie-based opt-outs are not effective on mobile applications. However, on many mobile devices, application users may opt out of certain mobile ads via their device settings.

The online advertising industry also provides websites from which you may opt out of receiving targeted ads from our data partners and our other advertising partners that participate in self-regulatory programs. You can access these, and also learn more about targeted advertising and consumer choice and privacy, at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>, or <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>and <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>, or [https://preferences-mgr.truste.com](https://preferences-mgr.truste.com/).

To be clear, whether you are using our opt-out or an online industry opt-out, these cookie-based opt-outs must be performed on each device and browser that you wish to have opted-out. For example, if you have opted-out on your computer browser, that opt-out will not be effective on your mobile device. You must separately opt out on each device. Advertisements on Third-Party websites that contain the AdChoices link and that link to this Privacy Policy may have been directed to you based on anonymous, non-Personal Information collected by advertising partners over time and across websites. These advertisements provide a mechanism to opt out of the advertising partners’ use of this information for interest-based advertising purposes.

—————-

Parents, please explore Funology — we think you will agree it is a great place to be. If you have any questions about our privacy policies, or anything else, e-mail us at inquiries (at) funology.com.

Big Fish Design, 15486 Waters Creek Drive, Centreville, VA 20120 TEL: (703) 502-1321 E-MAIL: inquiries (at) funology.com
